<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>SilentGlasses</title><subtitle>A minimal, portfolio, sidebar, bootstrap Jekyll theme with responsive web design and focuses on text presentation.</subtitle> <updated>2021-12-27T12:03:58-06:00</updated> <author> <name>SilentGlasses</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2021 SilentGlasses </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Git Best Practice</title><link href="/posts/git-best-practices/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Git Best Practice" /><published>2021-12-22T04:30:00-06:00</published> <updated>2021-12-22T04:30:00-06:00</updated> <id>/posts/git-best-practices/</id> <content src="/posts/git-best-practices/" /> <author> <name>{"name"=>"SilentGlasses", "link"=>"https://github.com/SilentGlasses"}</name> </author> <category term="DevOps" /> <category term="Git" /> <summary> These are just a collection of things I find interesting for myself and may not be for everyone. Keep your commits small and clean When working with changes to fix bugs, it’s easy to get sidetracked and work on multiple bugs as you see them. It’s fine to work on multiple things at the same time in a repository but you want to keep each commit small and focused. You can later squash your com... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>gitignore</title><link href="/posts/gitignore/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="gitignore" /><published>2021-12-22T04:25:00-06:00</published> <updated>2021-12-22T04:25:00-06:00</updated> <id>/posts/gitignore/</id> <content src="/posts/gitignore/" /> <author> <name>{"name"=>"SilentGlasses", "link"=>"https://github.com/SilentGlasses"}</name> </author> <category term="DevOps" /> <category term="Git" /> <summary> Introduction The .gitignore file is a simple text file that tells Git which files and folders in a repo it should ignore. These files can be stored at the repo level or at the global level. To get a good setup for your needs, you can use gitignore.io to create your file with the entries you need. WARNING: Files already being tracked by Git are not affected by adding this file. To use a globa... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Using Git on macOS</title><link href="/posts/using-git/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Using Git on macOS" /><published>2021-12-22T03:58:00-06:00</published> <updated>2021-12-22T03:58:00-06:00</updated> <id>/posts/using-git/</id> <content src="/posts/using-git/" /> <author> <name>{"name"=>"SilentGlasses", "link"=>"https://github.com/SilentGlasses"}</name> </author> <category term="DevOps" /> <category term="Git" /> <summary> Git on macOS Before proceeding, ensure that you have your SSH properly setup and configured. Using SSH Keys tutorial coming soon. Xcode Install Xcode by running this command in your terminal xcode-select --install Using Homebrew You should already have Homebrew installed. Using Homebrew tutorial coming soon Run the following command to install Git brew install git The manual way ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Reset NVRAM, PRAM or SMC</title><link href="/posts/mac-smc-pram/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reset NVRAM, PRAM or SMC" /><published>2021-12-22T03:20:00-06:00</published> <updated>2021-12-22T03:20:00-06:00</updated> <id>/posts/mac-smc-pram/</id> <content src="/posts/mac-smc-pram/" /> <author> <name>{"name"=>"SilentGlasses", "link"=>"https://github.com/SilentGlasses"}</name> </author> <category term="Hardware" /> <category term="macOS" /> <summary> Reset NVRAM or PRAM NVRAM or NonVolatile Random-Access Memory is a small amount of memory that your Mac uses to store certain settings and access them quickly. PRAM (Parameter RAM) stores similar information, and the steps for resetting NVRAM and PRAM are the same. These settings include: sound volume display resolution startup disk selection time zone recent kernel panic in... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Cron</title><link href="/posts/cron/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cron" /><published>2021-12-22T03:10:00-06:00</published> <updated>2021-12-22T03:10:00-06:00</updated> <id>/posts/cron/</id> <content src="/posts/cron/" /> <author> <name>{"name"=>"SilentGlasses", "link"=>"https://github.com/SilentGlasses"}</name> </author> <category term="Administration" /> <category term="Utilities" /> <summary> Cron is a time-based job scheduler in Unix-like computer operating systems. People who set up and maintain software environments use cron to schedule jobs (commands or shell scripts) to run periodically at fixed times, dates, or intervals. Cron is driven by a crontab (cron table) file, a configuration file that specifies shell commands to run periodically on a given schedule. The crontab files... </summary> </entry> </feed>
